moneylife.in 2018-12-24

# Moneylife India

PRIVACY POLICY

**Privacy Statement and Terms of Use**

This Privacy Statement relates solely to the online information collection and use practices of our Website located at www.moneylife.in its subdomains and www.suchetadalal.com (“Websites”). We recognize that many visitors and users of these Websites are concerned about the information they provide to us, and how we treat that information. This Privacy Statement, which may be updated from time to time, has been developed to address those concerns.

Your use of these Websites indicates to us that you have read and accept our privacy practices, as outlined in this Privacy Statement. If you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact: mail[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**What Information Do We Collect?**

When you visit these Websites, you may provide us with two types of information (1) personally identifiable information that you knowingly choose to disclose, which is collected on an individual basis, and (2) general user information that does not contain personally identifiable information, which is collected on an aggregate basis as you browse the Websites. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with requested information, you may not be able to access all of this Websites’ content or services.

**Personally Identifiable Information You Choose to Provide**

We may ask for certain personal information from you which is necessary to provide you with the content and/or services you request. Some of the services which ask you to provide personal information include:

Newsletters and subscriptions

Phone Alerts

Email alerts

Contributing to blogs

Sharing pictures and videos

Submitting questions or editorial feedback

Non-Personally Identifiable Information That We Collect.

Cookies/Web server logs: Similar to other commercial Websites, these Websites utilizes standard technology called “cookies” and Web server logs to collect information about how these Websites is used. Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Website. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s Web browser on the user’s hard drive. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at these Websites, and the Websites visited just before and just after these Websites. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.

You can, of course, disable cookies on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our Websites will not operate correctly if you disable cookies. You should consult with your browser’s provider/manufacturer if you have any questions regarding disabling cookies.

**How Do We Use the Information We Collect?**

We use your personally identifiable information to provide you with the information or content that you have requested. We will not send you any marketing material unless you have requested it through the Websites.

Further information about how we use your personal information is provided on our web-pages at the point you submit your personal information to us.

We use non-identifying information collected on our Websites in the aggregate to better understand your use of the Websites and to enhance your enjoyment and experience. For example, we may use the information to improve the design and content of our Websites or to analyze the programs and services that we offer.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Our employees, agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.

We may provide access to your personally identifiable information when legally required to do so, to co-operate with police investigations or other legal proceedings, to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of these Websites, to limit our legal liability and protect our rights, or to protect the rights and safety of visitors to these Websites or the public. In those instances, the information is provided only for those limited purposes.

We will not share your personally identifiable information in ways unrelated to those described above without providing you with an opportunity to opt out of such use or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Data Security**

We take reasonable steps to maintain the security of the personally identifiable information that we collect, including limiting the number of people who have physical access to our database servers, as well as installing electronic security systems that guard against unauthorized access. However, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. Accordingly, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, so you do so at your own risk.

**Links**

This Website contains links to third party sites as well as to other sites owned and/or operated by Moneylife group. Please be aware that Moneylife group is not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party sites. Please also be aware that the privacy policies of other Moneylife sites may differ from the privacy policy of this Website. Therefore, we encourage our users to read the privacy statement of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Statement applies solely to information collected by this Website.

Copyright © 2016. All rights reserved by Moneylife and Moneylife Digital Pvt Ltd.
